## **Ezz Elden Mohamed**

### **Front-End Developer**

El Mansoura , El Dakahleya | <u>+201002368023</u>| <u>ezzelden4work@gmail.com</u> <u>My WebSite</u>, <u>linkedin</u> , <u>codepen</u> , <u>GitHub</u> , <u>Youtube</u>

## **Summary**

I'm a front-end web developer. I have 5 years of experience in this field. You can say that I'm a full-time Web developer in addition to being a student. I'm passionate about keeping up with everything new in technology trends, I have my personal touch at my work. you can be keen on me for any project you need to do.

#### **Education**

I'm Graduated from Delta College of Management Information Systems 2022

#### **Skills**

Html | css | Javascript | jQuery | BootStrap | Sass | Next.js | React.js | React Native | GitHub | CssAnimation | AdobeXD | Figma | Php | WordPress

## **Professional Experience**

#### **Buraq**

Sap 2022 - Dec 2021

Front-end Web Developer

Some of Project:

- <u>Twision</u>
- Shams Store
- Todo pazer

#### **Atheltree**

Jan 2021 - Dec 2021

Front-end Web Developer

#### Some of Project:

- Survey
- Round Base

Web Instructor: 2021

I was giving some web development courses in my college by assembling groups of students and starting how to develop the website professionally.

#### **Graduation projects Assistant:**

2021

I was assisting students in their graduation projects, supervising them in the design and development stages, and discussing them in front of a specialized committee of doctors in the fields of technology.

Some of Project:

- <u>Elfahd Elevetor</u>
- Smart Parking
- Elkepash

Jan 2020 - Jan 2021 The Lean

• Front-end Web Developer

Some of Project:

- Store Demo
- Youssef Allam Group
- Khozam

#### **Afro Arab Digital**

Feb 2020 - July 2020

Front-end Web Developer

Some of Project:

- Afro Arab Digital
- Bakkahlean

Oct 2017 - Feb 2020 Devolum

• Front-end Web Developer

Some of Project:

- Alemnishokran
- <u>Midstr</u>
- Islah
- Oral

# **Projects**

Vuesax Dashboard gitHub Live View

- Dark & Light Mode
- Chat Page

Round Base <u>gitHub</u> <u>Live View</u>

- React.js
- Company Review

Elkebash Site <u>Live View</u>

- WordPress
- Ui/Ux

See More Projects.....

Langues

Arabic : Native | English : Good Write and Speak